Ayoub Mouloua

Cybersecurity Consultant

Casablanca, Morocco■ contact@ayoub0x1.me+212616342948■ MoroccanBin ayoub0x1ayoub0x1□ ayoub0x1#4552✓ Ayoub0x1♦ https://app.hackthebox.com/profile/803489★ https://ayoub0x1.me

₽ PROFILE

Experienced in the realm of cybersecurity, I possess comprehensive proficiency in various domains including penetration testing, red teaming, risk management, unauthorized access, viruses, managing networks, server administration, and a vast array of vulnerabilities and threats. Furthermore, I am adept in both direct and remote analysis, with exceptional critical thinking, communication, and interpersonal abilities.

EDUCATION

English literature, Moulay Ismail UniversitySep 2019 – presentEnglish Studies as a second majorMeknes, Morocco

42 Associate degree, 1337, 1337 school Sep 2021 – Sep 2022 IT training in several fields: Information security, programming, networking... Khouribga, Morocco

Baccalaureate, Manfalouti high schoolSep 2018 – Jun 2019Baccalaureate degree in physics and chemistryMeknes, Morocco

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Cybersecurity Consultant, Techso Group

Aug 2023 – present Casablanca, Morocco

Jun 2022 - Aug 2023

Casablanca, Morocco

Cybersecurity Consultant, CapValue

- External & Internal Penetration Testing
- Web Application Penetration Testing
- Mobile Application Penetration Testing
- Report writing

Bug Bounty Hunter, HackerOne & Synack

Participated in many public and private bug bounty programs through the responsible disclosure of security vulnerabilities in various web technologies and applications to high-profile organizations. Some statistics include but are not limited to:

• Found and Reported several security vulnerabilities and got fixed.

Over 20 acknowledgments were received (U.S. Dept Of Defense, AT&T, IBM, Semrush, Moneybird, Automattic, Hyatt Hotels, etc.).

• Reference: hackerone.com/ayoub0x1

Apr 2020 – present Remote

⊗ SKILLS

Programming & Scripting \bullet \bullet Web Penetration Test \bullet \bullet C/C++/Python/BashManual/Automation Audit, vulnerability assessment

Networking SIEM / SOC
Routing, Network security SIEM / SOC
Elastic stack, Prometheus

PUBLICATIONS

CVE-2022-2365, zadam

Description: CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')

CVE-2022-4734, usememos

Description: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitHub repository usememos/memos

Ø3	т /	A B.T	CI	т А	CE	
NE-Q	1.4	$ \mathcal{L}$	(+1	IΔ	(÷ H	•

Arabic English English

contact@ayoub0x1.me 1/2



Introduction to Cybersecurity Cisco

Certified Red Team Professional (CRTP)

Pentester Academy

contact@ayoub0x1.me 2/2